(Penny:)If you don't stay awake,
we'll never finish.
I'm sorry. Coffee is out of the question.
(Sheldon:)When I moved to California, I promised my
mother that I wouldn't start doing drugs.
(Penny:)Leonard, help.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, we still have 380
of these things to make.
I have faith that you will make them.
Good night.
(Howard:)- Leonard.
- Yeah... No.
(Leonard:)But, Sheldon, without your insight and
leadership, this enterprise will surely fail.
(Sheldon:)You're right, of course.
(Penny:)Here, this will help.
(Sheldon:)Very well.
(Sheldon:)But if this leads to opiates
or hallucinogenics...
...you're gonna have to answer
to my mother.
(Sheldon:)Look at Planck's constant.
People say that's arbitrary.
That could not be less arbitrary.
If it varied even slightly...
(Sheldon:)...life as we know it would not exist. Bam!
(Sheldon:)Now, now, let's reconsider the entire
argument but with entropy reversed...